cast thread

alfredo - rapier or long bow?
long bow can have shield

Cartography reaction...
Cooldowns.py?

Alright - cooldown bug.  Two clocks being used, calling misc's "wait" doesn't work because SmartCombat and Kill.py use a __class__ variable.
Plan: Let Kill keep the variable, but still have misc functions implement the wait.  
Plan: Make a Cooldowns object to implement the waits.  It can "look at" the __class__ variable owned by Cast and Kill...
- So this means that "Go" has less power than "Kill" when it comes to that cooldown.  By "power" I just mean that Kill owns it... which doesn't change much it just is.
Current: SmartCombat doesn't work but kk does because kk uses misc waits.
1. Implement Cooldowns waits
2. Make SmartCombat use them
3. (Cleanup) update kk to change which waits it uses (we don't want 2 sets of waits...)
So Cooldowns is an object I suppose meaning its variables are instance variables... nono we definitely want them singletons (class variables.)  Cooldowns can be instantiated for reaction purposes but some of its variables are class variables.
Take all cooldown variables out of Character (hasting)
Yikes, Command, Kill/Cast, and Cooldowns.  How about Cooldowns is registered all the time and Kill/Cast never get registered and you don't have to make an object.  Bam.  How do the threads die?  They register themselves for different reactions.  Who owns the timers?  Cooldowns, since its registered.
- So Kill and Cast don't have to inherit Command.  Abilities can.  Don't go too crazy with classes, just do it enough for the common code for abilities.  Do up a custom ability object for each ability dynamically once you know the class.  "Command" is cooldown infrastructure.
- (Do abilities hit the global cooldown?  Some hit the attack cooldown, some hit the move cooldown...
- Command can still be used but we need more granularity... CMPT250 all over again
- Does each ability have a class.  Well... there will be an Ability class.  Each ability OBJECT needs a timer(?) Or Cooldowns will code each ability.  That seems simpler!  Let Cooldowns do everything.  Make the objects SmartCombat needs dynamically.  Give them the functions SmartCombat needs (up()).  I think the ability object can have the timer variable because the alternative is too complicated - Cooldowns would need timers ready for EVERY ability.
- On startup, make and toss in the Ability reaction - that will work for human use, and also put it where SmartCombat sees it.  The Ability reaction can kick Cooldowns.move_clock - Cooldowns can be a tramp.  
- To use an ability, do you need access to the object??  Humans just type in the command, and the bot uses SmartCombat. This solves the issue for Kill too - let humans just type the command - no need to make an object each time.  So maybe Kill can handle its own timer???  How about that - trust the human to know the comman and forget the idea about needing to instantiate an object - Let Kill and Cast get tossed in on startup (singletons,) and they'll watch to get their cooldowns, and the wait() can be a static method.!  Yikes, I dunno!!!  The human, and killThread even, don't use the Kill object which is a reaction, they just type into telnet.  Ehh... how about they use a class method so that the cooldown gets set right.
- There will be a class for each ability.  Each class will needs its own timer and possibly wait method, although perhaps something as high as BotReaction can implement a wait method that will work on the subclass's timer.  Making the timer and wait methods class variables allow the human user to access the wait method without having the instance.  Each ability is on the same level as Kill and Cast.  Kill and Cast will have one object registered to maintain the cooldown.  Cooldowns will have class methods to look at these variables, and so will Kill and Cast and each ability.  
- Differentiate the BotReaction wait method (lag) from the class level wait method (cooldown)
- So los-helper will register all this stuff... it could be done by init but that takes away some freedom to make one if you want.  Right now Whois registers/unregisters itself when you hit execute.  This is fine because it's a one-shot.  Other command will be registered by los-helper (never to be unregistered, while whois and info get unregistered.)
los-helper:
kill = Kill(self.mudReaderHandler, self.telnetHandler)
self.mudReaderHandler.register_reaction(kill)
Kill.execute_blocking("dustman")  # The reaction has to hit a class variable
 # So we can't inherit the flag so we can't use BotReactionWithFlag
Kill.wait_for_flags
How about a singleton where the object is a class variable
import globalPackage
veryGlobalReachingClass: def __init__(self):
self.inventory = globalPackage.veryGlobalReachingClassObject


(That shopping thing is annoying (auto-inventory when something's bought).